Guide to the Samuel L. Clemens Papers, 1796-1984 (bulk 1853-1909)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series AA. Annie Moffett Webster Correspondence
  - Guarantee from George M. Newton and William Bookslaver to AMW, Dunkirk, NY, 13 May 1891 (24.54 [AA.5])
  - Sales contract, Annie M. Webster to Etta E. Hooker for sale of Central Ave. house, Fredonia, NY, 2 Aug 1904 (24.55 [AA.6])
  - Letter to AMW, Bank of Central California, Fresno, CA, 5 Oct 1908 (24.56 [AA.7])
  - Telegram for AMW from SLC, Redding, CT, undated; [Original with Mark Twain 1909 letters (B.629)] (24.57 [AA.8])
  - Letter from Albert Bigelow Paine, Brook Place, Redding, CT, 28 Oct 1912 (24.58 [AA.9])
  - Announcement of marriage of Louise Kirby Paine to Mr. John Conklin Benjamin, 4 June 1917 (24.59 [AA.10])
  - Letter from AMW to Ethelyn, 700 West End Ave., NYC., 26 June 1917 (24.60 [AA.11])
  - Card from AMW to Ethelyn, 700 West End Ave., 30 Aug 1917 (24.61 [AA.12])
  - Postal to Ethelyn McKinney, 17 July 1917 (24.62 [AA.13])
  - Letter from R. Rathbun, Smithsonian Institution, 8 Nov 1916 (24.63 [AA.14])
  - Letter from W. deC. Ravenel, Smithsonian Institution, 29 Jan 1918 (24.64 [AA.15])
  - Receipt for letter of J.K. Wallace, Smithsonian Institution, 15 Feb 1918 (24.65 [AA.16])
  - Copy of letter from Gen. S.B. Buckner to U.S. Grant. Headquarters, Fort Donelson, 16 Feb 1862 (24.66 [AA.17])
  - Copy of letter from Sen. S.B. Buckner to Maj. Cosby. Headquarters, Fort Donelson, 16 Feb 1862 (24.67 [AA.18])
  - Letter from Gen. Buckner to Brig. Gen. U.S. Grant. Headquarters, Dover, Tennessee, 16 Feb 1862 (24.68 [AA.19])
  - Receipt for $200 payment…signed by J.K. Wallace. New York, 27 July 1885 (24.69 [AA.20])
  - Letter from M.V. Sheridan Military Secretary. Headquarters, Army of the US, 9 June 1885 (25.1 [AA.21])
  - NY Times clipping: "After 97 years a working copy of the surrender agreement between Gen. U.S. Grant and Gen. Robert E. Lee was returned to Appomattox today…", undated (25.2 [AA.22])
  - Copy of letter from U.S. Grant to R.E. Lee. Appomattox Court House, VA, 9 Apr 1865 (25.3 [AA.23])
  - Letter to AMW from Rockwood and Lark, 527 5 Ave., NYC, 23 Jan 1919, 2 Dec 1918, 6 Dec 1918 (25.4 [AA.24])
  - Letter from AMS. Steamer Rochambeau, 26 Aug 1920 (25.5 [AA.25])
  - Letter to Miss Sands from AMW of 61 E. 86 St., NYC, 28 Apr [no year] (25.6 [AA.25A])
  - Letter to Ethelyn from AMW of 61 E. 86 St., NYC, 28 July 1921 (25.7 [AA.26])
  - Letter to Ethelyn from AMW of 61 E. 86 St., NYC, 6 July 1921 (25.8 [AA.27])
  - Letter to Lean from AMW of 61 E. 86 St. NYC, 4 May 1925 (25.9 [AA.28])
  - Letter from William Lyon Phelps, Yale University, New Haven, 18 Jan 1926 (25.10 [AA.29])
  - Letter to Ethelyn from AMW of 17 Park Ave., NYC, 7 Oct [no year] (25.11 [AA.30])
  - Annie M. Webster, USA Passport No.644695, 26 Oct 1928 (25.12 [AA.31])
  - Annie M. Webster, USA Passport No.477076, 20 Sep 1937 (25.13 [AA.32])
  - Postal to JWMcK, London, 2 Aug [no year] (25.14 [AA.33])
  - Postal to JWMcK, Maseira, 23 Jan 1929 (25.15 [AA.34])
  - Postal to JWMcK, Jerusalem, 5 Jan 1929 (25.16 [AA.35])
  - Postal to JWMcK, Bombay, 27 Feb 1929 (25.17 [AA.36])
  - Postal to JWMcK. Kobe, Japan, 21 Apr 1929 (25.18 [AA.37])
  - Postcard: "Teached Pekin last night,", 14 Apr 1929 (25.19 [AA.37A])
  - Postal to Ethelyn, China, undated (25.20 [AA.38])
  - AMW to JWMcK with specimen of heather "which grows over the moors of Scotland….", undated (25.21 [AA.39])
  - Letter to Miss McKinney, Virginia Craftsmen, Inc., undated (25.22 [AA.40])
  - Poem in AMW's handwriting: "Youth is a mental quality…", undated (25.23 [AA.41])
  - Letter to Ethelyn from AMW of 17 Park Ave., NYC, 21 June 1934 (25.24 [AA.42])
  - Family Chronicle written by AMW for granddaughter Jean Webster McKinney, 26 Oct 1918 (25.25 [AA.43])
  - "Long, Long Ago," manuscript of AMW's memoirs for her granddaughter, Jean Webster McKinney, undated (25.26 [AA.44])
  - Long, Long Ago, undated; (typewritten copy) (25.27 [AA.45])
  - Manuscript, Annie Moffett Webster, undated (25.28 [AA.46])
  - Manuscript, Annie Moffett Webster, undated (25.29 [AA.47])
  - Letter to Ethelyn from AMW of 17 Park Ave., NYC, 23 Dec 1940 (25.30 [AA.48])
  - Clipping: "Twain's Niece Denies Charge She Fled in War," NY Herald Tribune, Feb 1944 (25.31 [AA.49])
  - Clipping: "More Twain Recollections," Richmond, Times-Dispatch, 4 June 1944 (25.32 [AA.50])
  - Clipping: "Twain at His Worst," Time Magazine, 12 June 1944 (25.33 [AA.51])
  - Clipping: "Lace Cap Legend, Niece Recalls Mark Twain as River Pilot," NY World Telegram, 5 July 1944 (Box 37 [AA.52])
  - Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery, San Marino, Cal. Letter from Dixon Wecter, Chairman of the Research group, 6 Oct 1947 (25.35 [AA.53])
  - Letter from Barry Benefield. The Century Co., 11 June 1920 (25.36 [AA.54])
  - Letter from Barry Benefield. The Century Co., 21 June 1920 (25.37 [AA.55])
  - Article by AMW: "Recollections of the Clemens family in St. Louis when Sam was a river pilot," The Twainian, Mar-Apr 1949 (25.38 [AA.56])
  - Obituaries, Annie Moffett Webster in the NY Herald Tribune and NY Times, 24-25 Mar 1950 (25.39 [AA.57])
  - Annie Webster, NYC Certificate of Death, 24 Mar 1950 (25.40 [AA.58])
  - Ledger containing Annie Moffet Webster's world cruise shopping list (35.1 [AA.59])
  - Ledger listing Annie Moffet Webster's "Places Visited,", undated (35.2 [AA.59])
  - Annie Moffet Webster's scrapbook of clippings relating to Jean Webster's Daddy Long Legs as well as Mark Twain (35.3 [AA.60])
  - The Sunbeam Album, Library of [Charles] Webster, 25 Dec 1871 ([AA.61])
- Series BB. Walter Janes' Published Works
  - The Harmonic Minstrelsey. Dedham, MA: A. Mann, 1807 (26.1 [BB.1])
  - Chart listing descendants of Walter Janes, undated (26.2 [BB.2])
- Series CC. Calvin Whitney Correspondence
  - Remnant of stock certificate No.270, Providence Bank, with notation in Calvin Whitney's handwriting, undated (26.3 [CC.1])
  - Deed: Samuel Pearce to Hulda Eddy, Providence, RI, 26 Mar 1796 (26.4 and box 37 [CC.2])
  - Deed: Thomas C. Dilleber to Calvin Whitney, Woodstock, CT, 25 June 1830 (26.5 [CC.3])
  - Deed: executed before Calvin Whitney, Justice of the Peace, Ashford, Windham County, CT, 2 May 1833 (26.6 [CC.4])
  - Letter from Joseph F. White, New York, 19 June 1834, 15 Aug 1834 (26.7 [CC.5])
  - Letter from Joseph White, New York, 29 Mar 1836 (26.8 [CC.6])
  - Letter from County Sheriff, Beverly, Randolph County, VA, 9 July 1838 (26.9 [CC.7])
- Series DD. Luther Webster and Maria Whitney Webster, His Wife, Correspondence
  - Card given to Luther Webster by his teacher, circa 1834 (26.10 [DD.1])
  - Luther Webster's Commission as Ensign, Connecticut Militia, 22 Aug 1842 (26.11 [DD.2])
  - Luther Webster's Commission as Lieutenant, Connecticut Militia, 29 May 1843 (26.12 [DD.3])
  - Letter from Mrs. Sophia Chandler Webster and Luther Webster to Mrs. Calvin Whitney and her daughter, Charlotte Center, Chautauqua County, NY, 1-2 Dec 1845 (26.13 [DD.4])
  - Letter from Sophia and Luther Webster, Charlotte Center, Chautauqua County, NY, 4 Sep 1846, 8 Sep 1846 (26.14 [DD.5])
  - Letter from Parthena Janes to sister Theresa Janes Whitney (Mrs. Calvin Whitney), Allendale, 20 June 1847 (26.15 [DD.6])
  - Letter from MWW, Charlotte Centre, NY, 5 June 1848 (26.16 [DD.7])
  - Letter from SCW, Charlotte Centre, NY, 19 June 1848 (26.17 [DD.8])
  - Letter from Mrs. Luther Webster, Charlotte Centre, NY, 19 Dec 1848 (26.18 [DD.9])
  - Letter from Mrs. Luther Webster, Charlotte Centre, 18 Dec 1849 (26.19 [DD.9A])
  - Letter from Luther and Maria Webster to Mr. Edwin Janes at 125 Broad Street Providence, RI, 6 Aug 1850 (26.20 [DD.10])
  - Letter from Mrs. Luther Webster, Charlotte, NY, 27 Apr 1851 (26.21 [DD.11])
  - Letter from Mrs. Luther Webster to sister Ellen Whitney. Charlotte, NY, 16 Sep 1851 (26.22 [DD.12])
  - Letter from Luther and Maria Webster to Mrs. Calvin Whitney, Charlotte, NY, 30 Sep 1851 (26.23 [DD.13])
  - Letter from Mrs. Luther Webster to Mrs. Calvin Whitney, Charlotte, NY, 21 Dec 1851 (26.24 [DD.14])
  - Letter from Mrs. Luther Webster to Mrs. Calvin Whitney, Charlotte, NY, 8 June 1854 (26.25 [DD.15])
  - Rallying Song: political handbill for Fremont and victory, undated (26.26 [DD.16])
  - Letter from Mrs. Luther Webster to Mrs. Calvin Whitney, Lincolnville, 16 Sep 1856 (26.27 [DD.17])
  - Two deeds and receipt, Forest Hill Cemetery, Fredonia, NY, 13 May 1858, 29 Apr 1891 (26.28 [DD.18])
  - Letter from Mrs. Luther Webster, Fredonia, 15 Mar 1864 (26.29 [DD.19])
  - Letter from Mrs. Luther Webster, Fredonia, 26 Nov 1864 (26.30 [DD.20])
  - Letter from Cousin Nellie to Anna Whitney, Boston, 21 Aug 1869 (26.31 [DD.21])
  - Deed: "True Copy," Luther and Maria Webster convey to David H. Chandler, 1882 (26.32 [DD.22])
  - Luther Webster's Last Will, 6 Feb 1893? (26.33 [DD.23])
  - Letters Testamentary, Luther Webster, 15 Jan 1894 (26.34 [DD.24])
  - Notice of Probate of Will of Luther Webster, 19 Dec 1893 (26.35 [DD.25])
  - Family Record: Notes in Charles L. Webster's handwriting re: grandmother, undated (26.36 [DD.26])
  - Webster Family in England: CLW's notes from Sir Edward Burke's "Dictionary of Peerage and Baronetage,", 1874 (26.37 [DD.27])
  - Clippings: 2 fragments of article on Webster family genealogy from NY Times on occasion of 150th anniversary of birth of Noah Webster, the lexicographer, undated (26.38 [DD.28])
  - "Knowlton Family," genealogy copied from "Life of Gen. Nathaniel Lyon,", undated (26.39 [DD.29])
  - Births in Webster family, list beginning with Benjamin Webster, born 27 Jan 1798 (26.40 [DD.30])
  - Marriages in Webster Family" list beginning with marriage of Benjamin Webster to Sophia Chandler, 29 May 1823 (26.41 [DD.31])
  - Webster genealogy chart, undated (26.42 [DD.32])
- Series EE. Charles L. Webster Correspondence Sent
  - Business card: Charles L Webster, Surveyor and Civil Engineer, Fredonia, NY, undated (27.1 [EE.1])
  - State Normal and Training School, Fredonia, NY, letter to Mrs. Maria Theresa Whitney, 104 Clifford St., Providence, RI, from CLW, 30 June 1870 (27.2 [EE.2])
  - Letter from CLW, Charles L. Webster and Co., Publishers, NY, 4 Mar 1885 (27.3 [EE.3])
  - Charles L. Webster and Co. check for $1,000 to Gen. P.H. Sheridan, 6 Nov 1886 (27.4 [EE.4])
  - Charles L. Webster to Cardinal Gibbons, Baltimore, 13 Nov 1886 (27.5 [EE.5])
  - C.L. Webster's Letter Book: Copies of correspondence, 18 Oct 1885 – 27 Dec 1888 (27.6 [EE.6])
- Series FF. Charles L. Webster – Samuel L. Clemens Contracts
  - Charles E. Perkings, Attorney: Copy of minutes, Kaolatype Engraving CO. meeting of directors appointing Charles L. Webster Vice President and Treasurer of corporation, 29 June 1881 (27.7 [FF.1])
  - Charles L. Webster and Company Agreement No.1: Original partnership of Samuel L. Clemens and Charles L. Webster, 10 Apr 1884 (27.8 [FF.2])
  - Memorandum of Agreement: Gen. U.S. Grant and Charles L. Webster, 27 Feb 1885 (27.9 [FF.3])
  - Articles of Co-partnership No.2: Charles L. Webster and Co. made to publish the "Personal Memoirs of U.S. Grant,", 20 Mar 1885 (27.10 [FF.4])
  - Articles of Co-partnership No.4: Signed in duplicate [Charles] L. Webster, Fred J. Hall, S.L. Clemens, Olivia L. Clemens, 28 Apr 1885 (27.11 [FF.5])
  - Contract No.7: Permanent retirement of [Charles] L. Webster, 27 Dec 1888 (27.12 [FF.6])
  - Agreement to submit disputed Grant contract to Mr. George W. Childs for interpretation, 27 Feb 1885 (27.13 [FF.7])
  - Handwritten copy of above agreement, 27 Feb 1885 (27.14 [FF.8])
- Series GG. Charles L. Webster Notebooks
  - Mark Twain's Scrapbook: Charles L. Webster clippings (p. 1-29), Jean Webster clippings (p.30-40), Charles L. Webster articles (p. 100-108), undated (28.1)
  - Charles L. Webster notebook, Sep-Nov 1885, June 1887 (28.2)
  - Charles L. Webster ledger, 1 Oct 1880 (28.3)
- Series HH. Charles L. Webster Correspondence Received
  - CLW "Poll," with answers over signature of artists F.D. Millet, T.N. Bartlett, R. Swain Gifford, George Fuller, Augustus St. Gaudens, 24 Sep 1880 (29.1 [HH.1])
  - Pass to CLW to board "Constitution," NY Navy Yard, 9 Jan 1882 (29.2 [HH.2])
  - Notes on frigate "Constitution,", undated (29.3 [HH.3])
  - Letter from E.H. House, 23 May 1883 (29.4 [HH.4])
  - Letter from James R. Osgood and Co. to CLW, 3 Nov 1883 (29.5 [HH.5])
  - Letter from James R. Osgood Co., 13 Dec 1883 (29.6 [HH.6])
  - Invitation from NY Bar Assn. to reception of Right Honorable Lord Coleridge, 11 Oct 1883 (29.7 [HH.7])
  - Memo from Houghton Mifflin Co. to Mr. C.L. Webster, 6 Dec 1883 (29.8 [HH.8])
  - Letters from James R. Osgood Co. to C.L. Webster, 3 Oct 3 - 28 Dec [1883?] (29.9 [HH.9-30])
  - Letters from James R. Osgood Co. to C.L. Webster, 4 Feb 1884, 26 Mar 1884 (29.11 [HH.31-32])
  - Letter from Oliver Wendell Holmes, Boston, 15 Mar 1885 (29.12 [HH.33])
  - Letter from M.BM.H. Ticknor to C.L. Webster, 11 May 1882 (29.13 [HH.34])
  - Letter from W.D Howells, Boston, 8 Feb 1884 (29.14 [HH.35])
  - Fragment of letter signed William Cooper Howells, undated (29.15 [HH.36])
  - Letter from William Cooper Howells, Northampton, VA, 11 Feb 1884 (29.16 [HH.37])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, 4 Louisburg Square, Boston, 21 Mar 1884 (29.17 [HH.38])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 10 Apr 1884 (29.18 [HH.39])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, 4 Louisburg Square, Boston, 16 Apr 1884 (29.19 [HH.40])
  - Letter from William Cooper Howells, Northampton, VA, 17 Apr 1884 (29.20 [HH.41])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 4 May 1884 (29.21 [HH.42])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, 4 Louisburg Square, Boston, 9 May 1884 (29.22 [HH.43])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 11 May 1884 (29.23 [HH.44])
  - Letter from William Cooper. Howells Northampton, VA, 12 May 1884 (29.24 [HH.45])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 16 May 1884 (29.25 [HH.45A])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 8 June 1884 (29.26 [HH.46])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 10 June 1884 (29.27 [HH.47])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 16 June 1884 (29.28 [HH.48])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 21 June 1884 (29.29 [HH.49])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Wolfboro, NH, 30 July 1884 (29.30 [HH.50])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 4 Aug 1884 (29.31 [HH.51])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 18 Sep 1884 (29.32 [HH.52])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, 302 Beacon St., Boston, 27 Oct 1884 (29.33 [HH.53])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 27 Dec 1884 (29.34 [HH.54])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 8 Aug 1884 (29.35 [HH.55])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 28 Aug 1884 (29.36 [HH.56])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 2 Sep 1884 (29.37 [HH.57])
  - Letter from H.D. Howells, 4 Louisburg Square, Boston, 4 July 1884 (29.38 [HH.58])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, 302 Beacon St., Boston, 29 Mar 1885 (29.39 [HH.59])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, Boston, 10 Sep 1884 (29.40 [HH.60])
  - Postcard from W.D. Howells to CLW, 15 Sep 1884 (29.41 [HH.61])
  - Letter from Edmund C. Stedman, 44 E. 26 St., NY, 26 Oct 1884 (29.42 [HH.61])
  - Letter from J.T. Raymond, Denver, CO, 11 July 1884 (29.43 [HH.63])
  - Letter from J.T. Raymond, Chicago, 9 Sep 1884 (29.44 [HH.64])
  - Letter from J.T. Raymond. 8 East 32 St., 2 July (29.45 [HH.65])
  - Letter from J.T. Raymond, Park Theatre, NY, 25 Oct (29.46 [HH.66])
  - Letter from F.G. Whitman for S.L. Clemens, Hartford, 24(?) Mar 1884 (29.47 [HH.67])
  - Letter from R.N. Johnson, In the Catskills, Century Magazine, 21 July 1885 (29.48 [HH.68])
  - Letter from Henry M. Stanley, 15 Aug 1885 (29.49 [HH.68A])
  - Letter from Card. Vicario to Dr. O'Reilly (?), Roma, 7 Sep 1885 (29.50 [HH.69])
  - Letter from Thos. D. Galpin, Bristol House, Rosehampton, 17 Aug 1885 (29.51 [HH.70])
  - Letter from Thomas M. Walker, US Consul General, London, 14 Aug 1885 (29.52 [HH.71])
  - Letter from George Ticknor Curtis, 41 Mt. Vernon St., Boston, 29 Sep 1885 (29.53 [HH.72])
  - Letter from Anthony Comstock, New York Society for the Suppression of Vice, 26 Nov 1884 (29.54 [HH.73])
  - Letter from A.R. Spofford, Librarian of Congress, Library of Congress, Washington, 7 Oct 1885 (29.55 [HH.74])
  - Letter from C.A. Seward, New York, 11 Dec 1885 (29.56 [HH.75])
  - Letter from C.A. Dana, Editor, The Sun, NY, 23 Dec 1885 (29.57 [HH.76])
  - Letter from Roger Tichbourne, 25 Mar 1887 (29.58 [HH.77])
  - USA Passport No.2728: Charles L. Webster accompanied by his wife, 25 July 1885 (29.59 [HH.78])
  - Card used by canvassers for Personal Memoirs of US Grant, undated (29.60 [HH.79])
  - USA Passport No.6854: Charles L. Webster accompanied by his wife, 15 June 1886 (29.61 [HH.80])
  - Letter from Mrs. John A. Logan, Calumet Place, 4 Jan 1886 (29.62 [HH.81])
  - Letter from C.A. Dana, Editor, The Sun, NY, 14 Jan 1886 (29.63 [HH.82])
  - Letter from Rossiter Johnson. D. Appleton and Co., 20 Feb 1886 (30.1 [HH.83])
  - Billing from Dan Schwartzkopf and Co., NY, 6 Feb 1886 (30.2 [HH.84])
  - Billing from Bawo and Dotter, NY, 15 Feb 1886 (30.3 [HH.85])
  - Billing from Bauman Bros., NY, 13 Feb 1886 (30.4 [HH.86])
  - Billing from John H. Meeker, NY, 19 Feb 1886 (30.5 [HH.87])
  - Letter from C.W. Field, New York, 3 Mar 1886 (30.6 [HH.88])
  - Letter from Wm. E. Marshall, New York, 3 Mar 1886 (30.7 [HH.89])
  - Anonymous US passport: "An American,", 12 Mar 1886 (30.8 [HH.90])
  - Ellen M. McClellan, NY, 19 Mar 1886 (30.9 [HH.91])
  - Letter from Benson J. Lossing, The Ridge, Dover Plains, NY, 19 Mar 1886 (30.10 [HH.92])
  - Letter from Benson J. Lossing, The Ridge, Dover Plains, NY, 23 Jan 1888 (30.11 [HH.100])
  - Letter from A.R. Ward, 271 Broadway, 21 Mar 1886 (30.12 [HH.101])
  - Certificate from Wm. Bradford, New York, 13 Apr 1886 (30.13 [HH.102])
  - Letter from S.W. Crawford, 53 W. 21 St., NY, 16 Apr 1886 (30.14 [HH.103])
  - Envelope addressed to Mrs. C.L. Webster, undated (30.15 [HH.104])
  - Clipping re: [Charles] L. Webster's visit to Rome, undated (30.16 [HH.105])
  - Letter from Rev. Dr. O'Reilly, Rome, 27 Apr 1885 (30.17 [HH.106])
  - Letter from Cardinal Vicarius Urbis, Rome, 21 Mar 1886 (30.18 [HH.107])
  - Letter from General Longstreet, Gainsville, GA, 6 June 1886 (30.19 [HH.108])
  - Letter from G.P. Lathrop, 29 Washington Square, 18 June 1886 (30.20 [HH.109])
  - Letter from W.C. Prince, Charlestown, NH, 8 June 1886 (30.21 [HH.110])
  - Letter from W.C. Prince, 38 E. 23, undated (30.22 [HH.111])
  - Letter from W.C. Prince, 38 E. 23, 25 Feb 1885 (30.23 [HH.112])
  - Letter from W.C. Prince, 38 E. 23, 18 Mar 1885 (30.24 [HH.113])
  - Letter from W.C. Prince, 38 E. 23, 18 Mar [no year] (30.25 [HH.114])
  - Letter from James Cardinal Gibbons, Baltimore, 28 July 1886 (30.26 [HH.115])
  - Letter from Fred J. Hall, Charles L. Webster Co., 23 Aug 1886 (30.27 [HH.116])
  - Letter from T.P. O'Connor, 38 Grosvenor Rd., Westminster S.W., 23 Sep 1886 (30.28 [HH.117])
  - Letter from M.A. Corrigan, Archbishop, 452 Madison Ave., New York, 5 Nov 1886 (30.29 [HH.118])
  - Letter from James Cardinal Gibbons, Baltimore, 5 Nov 1886 (30.30 [HH.119])
  - Commissioner's Office, Police Dept. of the City of New York (30.31 [HH.120])
  - Letter from M.A. Corrigan, Archbishop, 452 Madison Ave. NY, 29 Nov 1886 (30.32 [HH.121])
  - Archbishop Corrigan to C.L. Webster?, 29 Nov 1886 (30.33 [HH.121A])
  - Letter from unknown correspondent, 251 E. 17 St., 3 Dec 1886 (30.34 [HH.122])
  - Letter from P.H. Sheridan, Headquarters, Army of the United States, 7 Dec 1886 (30.35 [HH.123])
  - Letter from Henry M. Stanley, Everett House, NY, 7 Dec 1886 (30.36 [HH.124])
  - Letter from T. McLaughlin, Church of the Blessed Sacrament, New Rochelle, NY, 7 Dec 1886 (30.37 [HH.125])
  - Letter from C.A. Dana, Editor, The Sun, NY, 20 Dec 1886 (30.38 [HH.126])
  - Letter from Gen. John A. Logan, Confidential, United States Senate, 5 Dec 1886 (30.39 [HH.127])
  - Letter from Gen. Logan, Senate Chamber, Washington, 9 Dec 1886 (30.40 [HH.128])
  - Letter from Gen. Logan,. Senate Chamber, Washington, 18 Dec 1886 (30.41 [HH.129])
  - Last letter dictated by Gen. J.A. Logan, Calmuet Place, Washington D.C., 22 Dec 1886 (30.42 [HH.130])
  - Letter from Gen. P.A. Sheridan, Headquarters, Army, Washington, DC, 21 Dec 1886 (30.43 [HH.131])
  - Letter from Gen. Wm. T. Sherman, 5th Ave. Hotel, NY, 25 Dec 1886 (30.44 [HH.132])
  - Letter from Gen. P.A. Sheridan, Washington, D.C., 28 Dec 1886 (30.45 [HH.133])
  - Received from Mr. Samuel L. Clemens $9,086.85, New York, 21 Oct 1887 (30.46 [HH.134])
  - Received by [Charles] L. Webster $5,000, New York, 26 Oct 1887 (30.47 [HH.135])
  - Gen. John A. Logan mourning cards, undated (30.48 [HH.136])
  - Letter from Mary S. Logan, Washington, DC, 8 Jan 1887 (30.49 [HH.137])
  - Letter from R.C. Bishop of Philadelphia, 225 North 18th St., Philadelphia, 20 Jan 1887 (30.50 [HH.138])
  - Letter from P.A. Sheridan. Headquarters, Army, 1 Feb 1887 (30.51 [HH.139])
  - Letter from G.W. Smalley, 8 Chester Place, Hyde Park Square W., London, 3 Feb 1887 (30.52 [HH.140])
  - Letter from Albion W. Tourgee, Mayville, NY, 7 Mar 1887 (30.53 [HH.141])
  - Letter from A.R. Hancock, Yonkers-on-Hudson, (1 or 7) Mar 1887 (30.54 [HH.142])
  - Letter from Rossiter Johnson, Editor. D. Appleton and Co., 17 Mar 1887 (30.55 [HH.143])
  - Letter from P.H. Sheridan, Washington, DC, 15 Mar 1887 (30.56 [HH.144])
  - Letter from the Office of E.C. Stedman, Broker, NY, 30 Mar 1887 (30.57 [HH.145])
  - Letter to Rev. O'Reilly, American College, Rome, 30 Mar 1887 (30.58 [HH.146])
  - Letter from P.H. Sheridan, Headquarters, Army, 17 Apr 1887 (30.59 [HH.147])
  - Letter from P.H. Sheridan, Washington, 29 Apr 1887 (30.60 [HH.148])
  - US postal card from Gen. G.T. Beauregard, 6 May 1887 (30.61 [HH.149])
  - Letter from E.C. Stedman, 44 E. 26 St., 13 May 1887 (30.62 [HH.150])
  - Letter from P.H. Sheridan, Washington, D.C., 21 May 1887 (30.63 [HH.151])
  - To Mr. C.L. Webster, Metropolitan Club, 1 June 1887 (30.64 [HH.152])
  - Letter from James Redpath, historian, 5 June 1887 (30.65 [HH.153])
  - Frank Bowles, New York, 13 June 1887 (30.66 [HH.154])
  - Letter from T.L. Smith, The Star, NY, 9 Aug 1887 (30.67 [HH.155])
  - Letter from P.H. Sheridan, Nonquitt, Mass., 1 Sep 1887 (30.68 [HH.156])
  - Letter from Archbishop Corrigan, 452 Madison Ave., NY, 8 Sep 1887 (30.69 [HH.157])
  - Letter from Bernard O'Reilly, Roche's Hotel, Glengariff, 16 Sep 1887 (30.70 [HH.158])
  - Letter from Bishop of Wilmington, Wilmington, DE, 16 Sep 1887 (31.1 [HH.159])
  - Letter from P.H. Sheridan, Nonquitt, 20 Sep 1887 (31.2 [HH.160])
  - Letter from A.P. Burbank, The Lotus Club, 23 Sep 1887 (31.3 [HH.161])
  - Billing from Bauman Brothers, 4 Oct 1887 (31.4 [HH.162])
  - Letter from P.H. Sheridan, Washington, DC, 6 Oct 1887 (31.5 [HH.163])
  - Letter from M. Sheridan, Washington, DC, 10 Oct 1887 (31.6 [HH.164])
  - Letter from M. Sheridan, Washington, DC, 12 Oct 1887 (31.7 [HH.165])
  - Letter from R.N. Johnson, Editorial Dept., Century Magazine, 19 Oct 1887 (31.8 [HH.166])
  - Letter from R.W. Gilder, Editorial Dept., Century Magazine, 17 Mar 1887 (31.9 [HH.167])
  - Letter from R.W. Gilder, Editorial Dept., Century Magazine, undated (31.10 [HH.168])
  - Letter from Joseph Jefferson, actor, New York, 20 Oct 1887 (31.11 [HH.169])
  - Letter from P.H. Sheridan, Washington, DC, 31 Oct 1887 (31.12 [HH.170])
  - Letter from James R. Fry, The Military Service Institution of the US, Governor's Island, NY, 2 Nov 1887 (31.13 [HH.171])
  - Letter from Gen. Sherman, Army Building, NY, 4 Nov 1887 (31.14 [HH.172])
  - Letter from Cardinal Gibbons, Cardinal's Residence, Baltimore, 15 Nov 1897 (31.15 [HH.173])
  - Letter from Gen. P.H. Sheridan written in the last days of his life, Washington, DC, 14 Jan 1888 (31.16 [HH.174])
  - Letter from Archbishop Corrigan, Archbishop's House, New York, 21 Jan 1888 (31.17 [HH.175])
  - Letter from R.W. Johnson, Century Magazine, 24 Jan 1888 (31.18 [HH.176])